globalcompliancepanel.com 2013-05-27

# Privacy Policy

GlobalCompliancePanel respects every individual's privacy. [www.GlobalCompliancePanel.com](https://www.globalcompliancepanel.com/) website is administered by NetZealous LLC and the primary purpose of GlobalCompliancePanel portal is to ensure secure online environment and also support your e-learning and development on/through our website. But at times we would need personal or general information to provide certain content or services, and online products on your request. This statement of the privacy explains personal or general data captured on our website or through other means by GlobalCompliancePanel and use of such information collected in those situations. 

The privacy policy expresses our commitment and discloses our privacy practices involved. It also keeps you informed about the information collected and how it is used. This policy is applicable to all the personal or general information we handle in our website. 

**Collecting Personal Information**  
GlobalCompliancePanel will collect personal/general information from the users of GlobalCompliancePanel website where you would be asked to fill your personal details by filling the online form for a secure user registration. However, it is completely optional for the users to engage in these activities. The personal information collected by GlobalCompliancePanel are your name, preferred language, country or location, postal zip codes, email address, telephone number, job title etc which will be used to create an "user account" on the GlobalCompliancePanel website to facilitate easier management of your time when you visit the GlobalCompliancePanel website for the second time & any time further which. 

This information is normally requested to be presented by you when you are subscribing to e-mail newsletters, user registration to enable enhanced service quality or purchasing products or services. Apart from this there could be additional information collected by GlobalCompliancePanel in order to fulfil your request order & to identify you while you call us for service requirements. 

Depending on the activity, certain information we may ask are compulsory to provide and some are voluntary. If you do not provide the compulsory data with respect to a specific activity, you will not be able to proceed further with that activity. When ordering the products or services through online web transactions, you may be asked to provide your credit card details over a very secure & reputed partner site such as pay pal or similar websites(may be included for better coverage at a later stage). 

When you submit your personal information to GlobalCompliancePanel website, you must understand that the information submitted is subject to transfer across the national boundaries and it could be saved and processed in the countries where GlobalCompliancePanel has & maintains offices. You must agree that in certain countries, with respect to certain activities, Global Compliance Panel's trusted vendors and partners would undertake the collection, transferring, storage and processing of your information. These vendors and partners are bound by critical contracts and they are not authorized to use your personal information for their own purposes or provide it to any third-parties. 

**Collected Information and Its Use**  
GlobalCompliancePanel needs to obtain at least the basic minimum information from the customer. The information may include e-mail address, unique customer identification number provided to you when a financial transaction has been successfully completed , department, job title, and password and other information. However, the information may not be limited to these. This information is used to enrol the customers in suitable webinar(s) and to direct them to information as requested by the Customer. GlobalCompliancePanel may use this information at the request of the customer to contact the students and send notifications, reminders and completion certificates. 

We may use the customer's information for new, unexpected uses which is previously not stated in our privacy notice. If the information practices change at any point in time, we will post the changed policy to our website and also provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. Keep checking our website often to know how your information is used. The customers have the right to prevent their information from being used for other purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by sending an e-mail to us at the address provided above. 

GlobalCompliancePanel gathers all your information in order to record and support your participation in the selected activities. If you subscribe to a service or register a product, for example, the information is used to register your rights, if any, to technical support or other benefits that may be made available to the registered users. Your personal information may also be used to keep you informed about the product upgrades, special offers and other products and services of GlobalCompliancePanel and services of selected third parties. 

GlobalCompliancePanel will disclose your personal information without any prior notice, only if it is necessary to do so by law or in good faith belief and such action is necessary to: 

  * Comply with legal process served on the site or conform to the edicts of the law 
  * Safeguard and defend the rights or property of GlobalCompliancePanel and its family of websites 
  * Act quickly under certain circumstances to protect the personal safety of the users of GlobalCompliancePanel, its websites or the public 

GlobalCompliancePanel examines the aggregate data including the number of users, number of users completing the courses, time spent on the courses etc and thereby improving the offerings and customer service. GlobalCompliancePanel compiles and uses this data for statistical analysis, marketing, or similar promotional purposes. 

The GlobalCompliancePanel visitors are not supposed to disclose any personal information on the public website www.GlobalCompliancePanel.com. We keep tabs on the visitor's activities in order to improve and enhance the performance of the website. If the visitor chooses to subscribe a newsletter, view a web cast or assess GlobalCompliancePanel's events, the personal information will be collected from the visitor for the survey and marketing purposes. The information may include name, title, company, email, phone number and more. The visitor information will not be shared with, rented to or sold to any third parties. 

**Security of Personal Information**  
GlobalCompliancePanel is very particular about maintaining the security of your personal information and respects your choice for its intended use. We carefully safeguard your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Also, your personal information is not shared with anyone outside the company at any given circumstance, without your permission, except under the above mentioned conditions. Within the company, the data is safely stored in the password controlled servers with limited access. 

**Your Information**  
For any further questions and concerns about your personal information, please contact GlobalCompliancePanel and include your name and user ID along with your concerns. You can also reach us after logging in to our website & by registering yourself as a user & raise a query. However, we are not authorized to change the customer proprietary information supplied to us without the authorization of the customer. 

**Changes**  
The privacy statement will be occasionally updated by GlobalCompliancePanel and you will be notified by placing prominent notices on the website regarding the material changes to this statement. 

**Acceptance of Privacy Policy Terms**  
GlobalCompliancePanel has the right to alter the policy at any time and the changes to this policy will be posted at the earliest. When we alter the policy, the new policy will apply to personal information previously collected. We recommend you to review this policy on a periodic basis to view any changes. Use of GlobalCompliancePanel constitutes acceptance of this policy. 

**Additional Information**  
For further queries on Privacy Policy, the practice of any GlobalCompliancePanel site or dealings with the GlobalCompliancePanel, please contact us at the following address: 

NetZealous LLC,  
161 Mission Falls Lane,,   
Suite 216, Fremont, CA 94539, USA. 

You can also email your concerns at [privacy@GlobalCompliancePanel.com](mailto:privacy@globalcompliancepanel.com) or call us at 1- 800-447-9407 .
